[Cough]
- Hi, Lennart, it's Pelle.
- Hi, Pelle.
[Cough]
- This bloody cough!
- Terrible!
It was good of you to come.
- Sorry, Lennart, didn't catch that.
- It was good of you to come!
Well sure, you asked me to,
but I can wait outside.
No, no, no. Stay here.
I'm flying to Barcelona at three.
Right then.
You're not pleased, so I hear.
No, actually I'm not, Lennart.
I think it's a shame.
This is no fun.
We'll soon be up to 700.
Who said anything about fun?
You know very well
we have to make it to a thousand.
You really mean that, Lennart?
I do.
[Splash]
Everything has its day, Pelle.
Yes, but...
The pyramids had their day.
Of course they did.
- Steam engines had their day.
- Sorry... didn't quite catch that.
Steam engines had their day.
That's true.
This is a new day and age, Pelle.
You have to realize that.
True enough, but still...
If this keeps up
we'll have to shut down entirely.
That would be a disaster
for a lot of people.
What's that got to do with us?
- You have a point...
- We won't be around then, Pelle.
Sorry, Lennart, what do you mean?
I mean, what's the point of staying
where there is only misery?
No, there's no point.
When that day comes
I'll be long gone...
...and so should you!
Beloved be the ones who sit down.
SONGS FROM THE SECOND FLOOR
Very nice!
Oh yes, the old boy
must look his best.
Pelle Wigert wants to
meet me today.
And what does he want?
We'll have to wait and see.
Lasse...
It would be nice if you could be
home today when I have my day off.
Sure, but how would that look?
I haven't missed a day in 14 years.
It would be nice just the same.
Everything has its day, dear.
There's a time for work
and there's a time
for other things.
No, no, no! No, no!
Everything has its day, dear.
You old bore!
Bye.
So long, traitor!
- Would you let go now!
- No, no, no, no!
- Pull yourself together, Lasse.
Pull yourself together!
I've been here for 30 years!
I'm sorry,
there's nothing I can do.
- I've been here for 30 years!
- There's nothing I can do.
I've been here for 30 years!
There's nothing I can do.
There's nothing I can do!
- But I've been here for 30 years!
- There's nothing I can do.
I've been here for 30 years, Pelle!
I've been here for 30 years!
[Knocking]
Yes?
Is there an Allan Svensson here?
No, there isn't.
He's not here!
Close the door!
Excuse me,
is Allan Svensson here?
What are you doing here?
What the hell are you doing here?
- He's talking to you.
- What do you want?
- I look for man, he not here.
- Speak clearly!
- What did you say?
- I look for man, he not here.
What's up?
- Who are you looking for?
- Allan Svensson.
What the hell are you doing here?
[He's screaming.]
Lasse... You-who?
What happened?
Such heavy traffic!
Even though it's so late...
What's wrong, Pelle?
We'll buy a new golf club.
We'll buy a new one!
May I have a volunteer?
Over here!
There's one there!
- Welcome up on stage!
No, leave me alone.
Please, come over here.
- May I take that for you?
- Sure.
Ow!
[Laughs]
[He's screaming.]
Ow! Ow! Ow!!!
[She's crying.]
When are you going
to get a divorce?
When will you do it?
Answer me!
Let's move along a bit then,
shall we?
Move? Oh. Right.
- There we go.
- Thanks.
[They are singing.]
You have to believe me, Krister.
You "have to" believe me!
I'm stuck here!
I haven't advanced more than
a few hundred yards in four hours!
- Hi.
Krister, I swear...
- Hiya.
Darling, what shall I do?
How are you?
What can I say?
It's not easy being human.
I agree.
- You saw your boy's there.
- Yeah.
He's been sitting and waiting
for hours.
You think I look like this
without reason?
No.
Dare I ask what you've done?
Done? I'm ruined.
My whole business
has burned to the ground.
What's that?
I said, the entire business
has gone up in smoke!
[The glass falls.]
Hi.
What have you done?
I'm ruined.
Don't you see?
My whole business
has gone up in smoke.
Look at this...
The books!
Nothing could be saved.
It's a fortune!
Maybe it's just as well...
Is that what you have to say to
your father, when he's in trouble?
I've been waiting for you.
I want to talk to you.
About what?
You know - the future.
How everything's going to... be.
What we're going to do.
How we're going to get by.
How we're going to put
food on the table.
Enjoy ourselves.
Does anyone know
how to get out of here?
No.
You could have called.
Something terrible has happened.
My whole business
has burned to the ground.
Nothing but ashes...
I'm the one who set fire to it.
And I think
I'll be discovered.
- Don't you see?
- Dear God!
I'm the one who set fire to it!
I think I'll be discovered.
[He's crying.]
You seen that crazy traffic
over there?
It hasn't moved in over 8 hours.
No one knows why.
It seems the whole town
is on the road.
Everyone going
the same direction.
Makes you wonder, you know,
where they're headed...
...the people.
Do you know where they're headed?
Where they are going?
Well...
- Do you want some bread?
- No, I'm fine, thanks.
- It's good. There's mustard on it.
- No, thanks.
You live around here?
Not any more.
What the hell
are you doing here, then?
I was just passing by.
I used to live up there.
At the top,
to the left of the drainpipe.
Really?
- I got thrown out.
- Thrown out?
Yeah, she didn't want me anymore.
Man, that's sad.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
God damn...
Ask me, I know.
What's her framerateFrom?
Susanne.
Susanne...
- Susanne, don't be so cruel!
- Shhh!
Open your door to a man
who hungers and thirsts.
Don't be so cruel, Susanne!
Damn, what beasts!
Maybe there's more...
Susanne!
Don't be so cruel, Susanne!
Open your door to a man
who hungers and thirsts.
Who the hell is that?
How do you know him?
I don't know who it is.
You've got to believe me, Micke!
It's true...
I don't know who it is.
Yes, well naturally,
I tried to put it out.
But it was impossible.
I was about to catch fire myself.
You see here before you
a fortune turned to ashes.
Everything seems
to happen to me!
One catastrophe after another.
Have there been other fires?
No, there haven't.
There are other catastrophes
besides fires.
That are much worse.
I have two sons.
The oldest...
...he's seriously ill.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, he's lost his mind.
Writing poetry made him nuts.
Oh dear!
Yes, it's terrible.
What's a few charred pieces of
furniture compared with that?
Nothing!
Of course, they were expensive.
Well... not this one.
But there was a Chippendale suite
over there.
A sofa.
Two armchairs.
Top quality!
78000.
Do you have that on paper?
Paper?
Obviously,
they've gone up in smoke.
But a Chippendale
is a Chippendale.
Even if it doesn't say
it on paper!
You, for example.
You are who you are,
whether or not
anybody's made note of it.
- Aren't you?
- I suppose.
Yep, we'll just have
to believe it.
This, this is my youngest son.
They're from
the insurance company-
- or so they say...
So, we'll just... have to take
their word for it.
[The crowd is screaming.]
In case you have trouble
understanding this,
you may as well
join the demonstration
and do some good.
Stock prices are falling.
The country's
in a very bad way.
They're fighting
for better times
and here you stand
and quibble over
a sofa and a few armchairs.
[Screaming]
Hi, Tomas!
Here we go again...
What have I done, Tomas?
What have I done wrong?
He's not answering.
He's not answering today either.
Can't even say "hi"
to his own father!
He's been writing poetry
and it made him nuts.
It's okay, Tomas.
The kids are fine.
Elisabeth too.
I drop by now and then.
You don't have
to worry about them.
Or about the cab.
I drive as much as I can.
It's a lucky thing
somebody's taking care of business!
He's left his cab and family
high and dry.
Writing poetry
till he went nuts.
It's awful! It's just awful!
[The father is crying.]
Beloved be the unknown man
and his wife.
My fellow man with sleeves,
neck and eyes!
Beloved be the one
who sleeps on his back.
The one who wears
a torn shoe in the rain.
Beloved be the bald man
without hat.
The one who catches
a finger in a door.
Catches a finger...
What's so special about that?
It's happened to everyone.
Writing poetry made him nuts.
Beloved be the one who sweats
out of pain or out of shame.
What kind of nonsense is this?
Give me my smock.
The smock!
The one who pays with
what he does not have...
There was a wallet here too.
Where is it?
Beloved be the ones
who sit down.
Sit down?!
- What's with that?
- Calm down now!
Beloved be the one
who sits down?!
Easy!
Why should you love him, eh?
- Look at that brother of yours.
- Take it easy!
He sits where he sits.
No yelling in here.
Calm down now.
Sit down, sit down...
He sits where he sits!
Who's going to come along
and love him, then?
Can no one help him?
It's good of the Father to let me
come and talk to him.
See, it's like this...
[He's crying.]
My entire business
has gone up in smoke.
It's nothing but ashes.
And I have a son
who's gone mad.
Makes you wonder
what you've done wrong...
You can't talk to him.
He doesn't respond.
I'm at my wits' end.
At your wits end...
So, who isn't?
I've been trying to sell
my house for four years.
No such luck.
Yep, I'll lose 200 thousand -
at least.
That's a shame.
A shame. A real shame.
What about me, then? I paid for
a trip and then the travel agency
went bankrupt, the money's gone.
It's all because
of the stock prices.
They... they go up and down.
- It's frightful!
- I quite agree.
Beloved be the one
who sits down.
I beg your pardon?
Beloved be the one
who sits down.
[Music]
We can go with this.
[She's crying.]
When are you going to do it?
You could answer at least!
It's nice to sit down
for a bit.
I've walked all the way
from North Station.
I thought...
"It'll be quicker to walk",
I thought.
In chaos like this,
that just goes on
without anyone being able to give
a reasonable explanation.
But it was a long way!
Longer than I thought.
I'm in a hurry. I'm late.
I overslept.
- I had nightmares.
- Oh dear!
Where are we going?
I'm going to visit our former
Commander-in-chief
who has a birthday today.
- He's turned a hundred.
- I see...
Where does he live?
Where do you think someone lives
who's reached such a venerable age
and who doesn't have
to pinch his pennies.
St. George's rest home.
St. George's. O.K.
A lot of people will be paying
their respects.
Admiral Bengtsson
is going to make a speech.
And can you guess
who wrote the speech?
No.
I did.
That's my main job these days,
writing speeches...
But it still makes me nervous
every time.
Terribly nervous.
Fact is, I had to nip into
the Grand Hotel and have a drink.
I needed one.
Well, three...
to be perfectly honest.
So now I'm actually quite
pleased with what I've written.
My approach was a rather
philosophical one.
About being human
year after year...
This is how I see it...
Life is time and
time is a stretch of road.
That makes life a journey, a trip.
- Don't you think so?
- Yes.
I guess you could
look at it that way.
Yet in order to travel you need
a map and a compass.
Otherwise you wouldn't know
where you were.
- Would you?
- No.
And our map and compass...
...are our traditions.
Our heritage, our history.
- Aren't they?
- Yeah, sure.
If we don't understand this...
Before we know it,
we're fumbling around in the dark.
Where are we?
Well, actually we haven't moved
more than a few yards.
- We haven't?
- No.
They keep delivering
more flowers!
Sure they do - when someone
celebrates his 100th birthday!
And has been so clever! Become both
a general and a millionaire!
Millionaire?!
To put it mildly!
He's one of the largest landowners
in the country.
20000 acres of cultivated land
and twice as much forest.
How much is that?
60000 acres.
How many square meters is that?
- 240 million, isn't it?
- Exactly!
Two hundred and forty million
square meters of land.
And eight lakes on his property.
- Fantastic!
- Unbelievable!
Really.
Uh-oh. I think it's time
for the bed-pan.
- Anna, the bed-pan!
- Coming...
They're here now.
Right honorable general and
Commander-in-chief Emeritus.
It is man's fate to grow older.
Year is added to year,
experience to experience
during our never-ending journey
around the sun.
Honored general and, if I may
say so, dear colleague.
Few people are privileged
to have completed such a
large number of orbits
around the sun
as you, sir, have done.
Today when you set out on
a new orbit, your 101st,
I, as an active member of
the joint Chiefs of Staff,
have the task, pleasure
and honor
on behalf of all branches
of the armed forces
to extend our hearty congratulations
to you,
sir as a person
and as a human being
and as a representative
of the safeguarding of our
country, our traditions
our distinctive character
and our history.
My best to Goering!
- I beg your pardon?
- My best to Goering.
Sound the regiment's
recognition signal.
Hoist the flags!
[Bugle]
- Where have you been?
- Sorry...?
Hi!
What do you mean, "been"?
I've been all over.
I've driven all over town
around and around...
...and listened to people
with problems.
I asked where you've been!
Yeah... and then...
Well, then I felt like
having a beer.
At least three, to be honest.
At least six, to be honest.
You could have called.
Seven, to be perfectly honest.
You didn't need to come here.
For Christ's sake,
should just sell
that damned car this minute.
Tomas can't drive a cab.
He's too soft.
He takes everything to heart.
What?!
What's wrong?
Am I not allowed here?
- Why not?
- You don't love me.
Beloved be the one
who sits down.
who sits down!
...who sits down.
Beloved be the one...
Rune...
"Do unto others"
"as you would have them do
unto you. "
In other words...
If you want me
to make you happy,
you have to make me happy.
Right?
But you haven't done that!
You've made me damned disappointed.
Have you seen the nails?
You come here, you sit down
and start talking business
without any cash.
Who the hell do you think you are?
I was thinking you could give them
to me on credit, Uffe. 30 days...
30 days?! Who the hell knows
what could happen to you in 30 days?
I'm really in a bind, Uffe.
Kalle! Well, I'll be damned!
- You're here this year too!
- Yeah, so they say...
Alive and kicking! And here I was
thinking you'd burnt to death.
How're you doing?
Oh, you know how it is, Uffe,
in times like these.
You have to struggle
for every crumb.
Try to find something you can sell
with an extra zero on the end...
In that case you've come to the
right place, Kalle. Take a seat!
- Hi, Kalle.
- Hiya.
- Sit down.
- Sure.
So, this is what you're up
to this year.
Yes, I too have to survive.
Here is the product you can put
two extra zeros on.
- You think so?
- Think?!
We're heading for the year 2000.
Two thousand, Kalle!
And this here is the birthday boy.
You get a chance like this
only once in a lifetime.
It'll be another thousand years
before this man
is as important again.
I guess I won't be around then.
This, this suits you, Kalle.
It suits an old furniture salesman.
Come here. Between you and me...
check it out.
There are already too many in
on the champagne
and fireworks.
Choose three sizes.
Take along an order-book.
Get out there and make some money!
Yeah... I don't know, Uffe.
I'm so tired.
I already have a cross to bear.
The insurance company
is giving me a hard time.
Besides my son has gone mad.
He what...?
Yeah, he's been writing poetry
and it made him nuts.
Well, it won't be a bread winner
but that'll blow over.
It'll blow over, Kalle.
- You think so?
- You shouldn't think so damn much.
It's not good.
[The man is screaming.]
- What happened?
- That's a good question.
He's stuck.
He's stuck in the door.
Well, that's pretty damned obvious.
But how did it happen?
He slipped, I guess.
- Slipped?
- Yes.
- How clumsy can you get?
- It could happen to anyone.
He slipped and fell backwards and
hit his other arm against the door.
- And it shut.
- Well, it's clumsy all the same!
Try to take it easy.
We'll help you in a minute.
My colleague will come and open
the door carefully from the inside.
Here he is now.
He's opening the door now.
- That's not so bad.
- That wasn't so bad now, was it?
It wasn't so bad.
It wasn't so bad, was it?
Poor man!
It could happen to the best of us.
Our son got himself stuck
in a deckchair last year.
- No, it was three years ago!
- Wasn't it last year?
No, it was three years ago.
What about me! I got my finger
caught in a dresser drawer
and it really hurt.
And that was ten years ago.
And look,
you can still see the gash.
- Hi.
- It's been ages...
- Yes, it has.
It really became barren.
- You really scared me, Sven.
- I did?
Yes, you did.
I suddenly felt really guilty.
When I caught sight of you, Sven.
You understand, I guess.
- You know what I thought?
- No.
As a matter of fact,
I thought you were dead, Sven.
I heard you'd committed suicide.
Yes, that's right.
For Christ's sake, Sven!
Why did you do that?
I had no choice.
Sven, am I to blame?
- Is it my fault?
- I didn't say that.
[Russian]
He's so unhappy, the poor boy.
- What does he want?
- He's gone astray, got lost.
- Are you looking for me?
- He's looking for his sister.
- Sister?
- Yes, his sister.
The Germans hanged her
over in Russia...
[Russian]
Then they hanged him too.
He's so very unhappy,
because he didn't have time
to apologize to her.
- If I've understood correctly.
- Apologize, for what?
He'd done something mean.
Hurt her, I think.
And regretted it, but he didn't
get a chance to make it up to her.
[Russian]
- Please!
- That's awful!
I can't bear to listen.
What had they done?
Why did they hang them?
Something to do with being
from the wrong race, I think.
- What?
- They belonged to the wrong race.
Oh dear, oh dear...
What happens now?
What's he going to do now?
- Who?
- The boy.
What do you mean, "do"?
He can't do anything.
That's why he's so sad.
Don't you see?
He didn't get a chance to make amends
with his sister before he died
while she was still alive.
Then he was hanging there
himself from the rope...
That's why it's so tragic.
Because he can't do anything
can't even try...
He's dead.
They both are.
Sven, how much
did I borrow from you?
Was it 280000?
No, I know, it was 287...
Excuse me for saying so, Sven,
I'm only being honest with you...
...but I was relieved
when I heard you were dead.
"Now I don't have to pay back
the money," I thought to myself.
There wasn't any papers.
I was free from my debt...
[Russian]
Good God, Sven,
what should I do?
I can't very well pay back
the money now, can I?
To me? That would be difficult.
I'm only human, Sven.
A man does the best he can
struggles to get a bit...
...of food on the table.
And enjoy himself.
Jesus...
He wasn't the son of God.
He was just a nice guy.
That's why he was crucified.
- He was tormented and killed.
- What?
He was tormented and killed.
- Who?
- Jesus.
- He was crucified.
- Of course he was.
Because he was a nice guy.
Hi, Tomas.
- Hello.
- Hi.
You could at least say "hi"!
- When your grandma's here and all!
- Take it easy.
Forgive me, Tomas.
I had something fun to tell you.
- I've got a new business concept.
- Me too.
I've got a business concept too,
but it's secret.
Imagine, Tomas...
The insurance company gave in.
And why do you think
they did that?
You've got to be able
to speak up for yourself.
Speak plainly
and you'll get results...
You can write poems
with words too.
It's not that.
Why complicate things, Tomas?
Life is a market.
It's as simple as that.
It's all about buying something
you can sell with an extra zero.
Or two.
The whole world knows that
everyone but you, it seems.
Is there no one
who can help you?
- Is there no one who can help you?!
- Take it easy!
Writing poetry
till you went nuts, huh?
Easy does it.
It's awful!
Is there no one who can help him?
...that's why he was crucified.
...who can help him?
- Calm down.
Is there no one who can help him?
It would of course
be an advantage
if the chairman of the Economic
Faculty's council of experts
could at this point present
at least the main features
of the long-term perspectives
and strategies
which the council would like
to propose to the government.
Long-term... I don't know if
I have those with me here today,
but the short-term ones
should be here somewhere...
One moment, please.
Strange. I'm sure I had them
this morning.
This is obviously not good.
It appears that we shall
have to skip the strategies
and concentrate
on tactics instead.
But before we do so, we should
perhaps attempt to summarize
what we've discussed here today.
It's difficult, I know.
Our discussion has lasted
over eight hours
but is there anyone who feels
they'd like to have a try?
Anyone?
Professor Frank, for example,
hasn't said anything
for a long time.
Well, I agree with
what most of the others
have had to say today.
All we can do is hope.
Would Dr. Wendt
care to comment on that?
The house across the street,
it's moving.
- I don't follow you.
- It's moving.
That house over there.
- What do you mean, "moving"?
- It's moving!
That's right, it is!
What kind of nonsense is that?
Hey...
It's moving...
- It is moving!
- It really is!
Take it easy! Take it easy!
The doors open inwards.
Back up! Hey!
It's very important
we don't lose control.
Very... important!
What papers
are you looking for?
What papers?
An official report.
A very troublesome report
which is supposed to clarify
why we can't afford to work.
You'll just have to write
a new one!
Try to remember what was in it.
Write a new one!
What was in it?
There wasn't very much in it.
It's hard,
it's very hard to explain
why we can't afford to work.
It's impossible!
It's not us who decide
that sort of thing.
We're not the ones who decide.
We must understand that.
It's fate that decides.
Not us. Fate.
Who can decide over fate?
Not us anyway.
All we can do
is try to appeal to fate.
That's all we can do.
[Russian]
You'll have to forgive me,
but I'm afraid I can't help you,
because I can't understand
what you're saying.
[Russian]
Like I said, I can't help you.
Help!
Ow! I'm stuck!
Enough is enough!
Get out of here!
Well now, Anna. From what
we've heard you're feeling fine,
not sick or anything.
- Yep, very healthy.
- I see.
- She's very healthy.
- She is, is she?
And you're doing well in school.
You're good at reading and writing
from what your mum and dad tell us.
I see.
- Have you read many books?
- Yes, a few.
I see.
You see, these ladies and gentlemen
sitting here...
...they've read all the books.
- That's right! An awful lot!
- Yes, most of them!
- Yes.
And when you've read that much,
well, then you also know
an awful lot.
Yes, and we also have
the benefit of experience.
Quite right.
Long experience, I might add.
Yes, indeed.
That's how you know
and how to do it.
And, Anna, there's one more thing
you know if you've read that much.
You know what can't be done,
what's impossible.
Exactly!
Because you can't do
just anything.
Certainly not.
An ant, for example, can't eat up
an elephant. It's impossible.
Right.
And when it's your birthday,
well, not everyone
can come to the party.
If they did, then everyone would get
a piece of cake this little.
- No bigger than a crumb!
- So small you could hardly see it!
- That wouldn't be such a fun party.
- No, darn it!!
I can see you understand that.
But there are other things, Anna,
that are impossible
and that can't be done.
That you can't really understand
when you're small
only when you're big
and have read many, many books.
And then there's also experience.
You mustn't forget that!
- No, absolutely not.
- No...
Aaaah!
[Music]
I can't get up.
Help! I can't get up!
We have sacrificed
the bloom of youth.
What more can we do?
Nothing.
- What?
- Nothing, absolutely nothing
What more can we do?
- Where are we?
- Huh?
Where are we?
At the Grand Hotel,
for Christ's sake!
Oh...
What more can we do?
What?
- But, where are we?
- I can't get up.
- Where are we?
What's wrong now,
then, Robert?
It's heavy, Pelle.
I can't take it any more.
You have to, Robert.
You have to try!
Come on!
Hang in there, Pelle!
You've got to hang on!
Yes, I know. I know.
- There's a time for everything.
- Sure, right.
Pelle!
There's a time for misery.
Sure, I know there is.
But it'll soon be over.
Only a few more yards
and we'll have left this damned
dump under the clouds for good.
Yes. Let's hope so.
- As free men, Pelle.
- Sure, right. Sure...
- Free at last!
- Yes!
And then we'll only have
ourselves to think about.
Right, sure, that'll be nice.
And do what we feel like!
Sure. Sounds good.
Do we not deserve that, Pelle?
Aren't we worth it,
when we've worked so hard?
Only a few more yards!
A new day is dawning!
Come on then!
There's a time for everything,
Tomas.
There's a time for everything.
Your time will come, Tomas.
It will... I know that.
It's not true that
no one cares about poetry.
They just pretend they don't.
Right now...
They're just pretending.
That's how it is. I know.
Beloved be the one who works
by the day, by the month,
by the hour.
Beloved be the one who sweats
out of pain or out of shame.
The person who goes, at the order
of his hands, to the movies.
The one who pays with
what he does not have...
The one who sleeps on his back.
[Tomas is crying.]
The one who no longer remembers
his childhood.
Stop it, Stefan!
You'll only make him unhappy.
You mustn't be unhappy, Tomas.
You mustn't cry!
Take it easy, Tomas,
it doesn't matter.
Beloved be the one
who sits down.
It's okay to cry.
That's what you should do
when you're unhappy.
- Jesus did.
- What?
Jesus cried when he was
on the cross.
He hurt so much.
He was crucified...
...because he was a kind person.
Kind?
Tomas is kind, too...
...but he's got no head
for business.
Of course you're unhappy!
Jesus didn't either.
He just hurt.
Yeah, sure.
He was tormented to death
because he was kind.
He wasn't the son of God.
He was just a kind person.
Sure.
Beloved be the just man
without thorns.
[Tomas is crying.]
The bald man without hat.
The thief without roses.
The one who wears a watch
and has seen God.
The one who has honor
and does not die!
Are you here, Uffe?
It's been a long time.
I'm ashamed, Kalle.
I'm ashamed.
- It was a bad idea.
- Yeah...
The worst I ever had.
Shit!
Damn it all!
How could I be so stupid?
Out of my mind.
To think you can make money
on a crucified loser!
God dammit,
I blush to think of it!
What a fucking dud product!
I haven't kept up
with the times!
That's the bitter truth.
But I'm going to get
my act together, Kalle.
We'll have to find
something else to sell
with a few extra zeros on it.
If I think of something...
I'll call. Bye, Kalle!
Is that Sven?
Is that you, Sven?
Why are you following me, Sven?
Why are you tormenting me?
I can't make it up to you.
How could I do that?
You have no relatives.
What can I do?
Sven!
Can we not treat each other
decently?
Forget it all.
The past...
Just look ahead!
I'd be really happy
if we could do that, Sven.
You have to see it
from my perspective.
I can't take it any more.
I can't take it any more!
I just can't take it any more!
What the hell is this?
How much can you ask
of a person?
You do what you can.
You struggle...
...to get a bit of food
on the table.
[He's crying.]
And enjoy yourself.
[Music]
Subtitling: CNST, Montreal
Ripped by:
SkyFury